thegoodlordabove.com 2018-03-13

# Privacy Policy - God

0

Welcome to TheGoodLordAbove.com!

Mysterious Ways, LLC., producer of TheGoodLordAbove.com, believes that electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial, and entertainment medium. We know you’re concerned about protecting your privacy online. This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you and how we use that information. In this Privacy Policy, “The God Website” or “the Website” means the website associated with the domain name TheGoodLordAbove.com. “The Services” means all the services offered in conjunction with the Website. “God” means Mysterious Ways, LLC., the owner of the Website and the provider of the Services. The term “Personal Data” refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your full name, birth date, e-mail address or mailing address, phone number and any other information that can be used to identify or contact you. By using the God Website, you consent to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. God reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy, and if we do, any such changes will be included on this page so current privacy information will always be available to you. We encourage you to check this page periodically.

 **No Collection of Personal Data from Children under 13.**

We recognize the need to provide additional privacy protections for the Personal Data of children under 13. The Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act (“COPPA”) requires general audience website operators to obtain a parent’s prior consent if they are knowingly collecting, using or disclosing any Personal Data from a child under 13. The God Website is not directed to or intended to be used by children under 13 (or under 18 for that matter), and God does not knowingly collect, use or disclose any Personal Data from children under 13. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [feedback@thegoodlordabove.com](mailto:feedback@thegoodlordabove.com).

 **Personal Data Collected.**

The only Personal Data God currently collects through The God Website is the Personal Data that you voluntarily provide to God. For example, users can signup for the newsletter to receive newsletter emails from the God Website. To signup, you must enter Personal Data, such as your email address. Users must also enter Personal Data, such as full name, address, phone number, email address, and credit card information to complete sales transactions in the God store.

Users may choose to use their existing “facebook” personal account information while visiting The God Website. If you choose to use facebook account information to gain access to The God Website, God will then be able to read and access all of your information, including Personal Data, posted on the www.facebook.com website.

Other data that does not qualify as Personal Data because it cannot be used to contact or identify you (“Non-Personal Data”) may also be collected when a user participates in certain features of The God Website, or may be automatically collected about you.

For example, God uses technology to automatically collect Non-Personal Data about the use of The God Website. This technology is used to track things like how many users access The God Website, the date and time of their visits, the length of their stays, and which pages they view. God may also use technology to determine which web browsers users use and the address from which they accessed the Websites. In addition, God uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting to collect Non-Personal Data about the use of The God Website such as overview of traffic by age and gender, as well as overview of traffic by affinity and other categories. The information collected using this technology does not identify any user personally and is thus all Non-Personal Data that simply enables God to compile statistics about users and their use of The God Website.

God uses this Non-Personal Data and may share it with third parties to improve the content and functionality of The God Website, to better understand our customers and markets, and to improve our products and services. We may also use this information to provide you with targeted advertising, so that the advertisements you may see on The God Website are of more interest to you.

Visitors may opt out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features by following [this link.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

 **Cookies.**

We may store certain information from your web browser using “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use session-ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies would terminate once the user closes the web browser. We may also use persistent cookies that store certain Personal Data you already provided to us to make it easier for you to log back in to The God Website or access your shopping cart. Cookies are used as a convenience feature for the user. You can remove or block cookies using the settings in your browser if you want to disable them.

 **Use of Personal Data Collected.**

God uses the Personal Data collected on the God Website to provide you with the requested Services. If you enter Personal Data to complete a purchase at God store, for example, that Personal Data will be used to complete your purchase and contact you with any questions related to that purchase.

God may also use the Personal Data to contact you for a variety of reasons, such as but not limited to notifying you about upcoming events, offering you additional products or services, or requesting your feedback on The God Website. If you wish to opt-out of these contacts, you can let us know by following the “unsubscribe” instructions that accompanied the contact email, or by contacting us at legal@thegoodlordabove.com. Even if you opt-out of certain contacts, God may still contact you about any problems or issues with your personal account.

 **Disclosure of Personal Data Collected.**

God may disclose Personal Data to third parties when (a) it is reasonably necessary to provide you with the Services, (b) you have authorized the disclosure, or (c) if required or authorized to do so by law.

God may also disclose Personal Data to third parties if a user has requested that God do so. The God Website may offer users opportunities to request disclosure of Personal Data to third parties. For example, users may have the ability to request through The God Website that certain third parties send them information. In that case, God would disclose the user’s full name and email address or mailing address so that the third party can send the user the requested information.

God may also disclose Personal Data to its affiliates, contractors and partners, who will use the Personal Data in compliance with this Privacy Policy. We may sell, rent, give or otherwise share your personal information with God’s successors, assigns, affiliates and other related third parties. God may also disclose Personal Data if required or authorized to do so by law.

 **Security Measures.**

God uses industry standard security measures to protect your Personal Data. While such security measures provide reasonable protections against unauthorized access, they provide no guarantee that your Personal Data will not be compromised.

 **Links to Other Websites.**

This Privacy Policy applies only to Personal Data collected on The God Website. The God Website may contain hyperlinks to websites that are not operated by God. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party websites or any association with their operators. God does not control these websites and is not responsible for their data practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any website you visit before using the website or providing any Personal Data about yourself.

 **Questions About Our Privacy Policy.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way God processes your Personal Data, please contact us at [feedback@thegoodlordabove.com](mailto:feedback@thegoodlordabove.com).
